Guide to the Freedom to Marry Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Audiovisual materials, 1986-2013; Series VII; 30.74; 360 boxes
  - General, 1989-2011
    - Every Family Matters: Lesbian, gay, bisexual & transgender familes & the marriage equality movement, 1 (Box 250)
    - Feagler & Friends #824 -27:26, 2004 June 11; 1 (Box 251)
    - For My Wife: for screening purposes only total run time: 56 mins Cinema Libre Studio, 1 (Box 252)
    - For My Wife: for screening purposes only total run time: 56 mins Cinema Libre Studio, 1 (Box 253)
    - For My Wife total run time 75:00 NTSC, 1 (Box 254)
    - For My Wife…a documentary film produced by David Rothmiller & LD Thompson trailer, 1 (Box 255)
    - Fox News Channel O'Reilly Factor 8pm-8:10pm, 2004 July 7; 1 (Box 256)
    - Fred: A film by John Fitzgerald Keitel, 1 (Box 257)
    - Free Shane and Josh, 1 (Box 258)
    - Freeheld 4 minute trailer, 1 (Box 259)
    - Freeheld 4 minute trailer, 1 (Box 260)
    - Freeheld copy, 1 (Box 261)
    - Garden State Equality video testimonials, 1 (Box 262)
    - Gay Marriage Debate Women's League synagogue, 2006 October 16; 1 (Box 263)
    - Gay Marrriage Forum, 1 (Box 264)
    - General Synod 25 wrap up video 7/4 Plenary on marriage equality 7/4 press conference, 1 (Box 265)
    - General Synod 25 wrap up video July 4 plenary on marriage equality July 4 press conference-John Thomas Statement, 2005 July 4; 1 (Box 266)
    - Gay & Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD) "Baker v. State of Vermont", 1 (Box 267)
    - Gay & Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD) video archive wes-quality clip, 2007 February 7; 1 (Box 268)
    - Good Morning America, 1999 August 5; 1 (Box 269)
    - Hawaii Marriage ads total run time - 12:00, 1998; 1 (Box 270)
    - Hawaii marriage forum, 1 (Box 271)
    - Heart of the Matter: Maryland's same sex couples seek justice for their families, 1 (Box 272)
    - Heroes - presentation pilot square 1 production, 1 (Box 273)
    - Human Rights Campaign "Protect our Constitution", 1 (Box 274)
    - Humans Rights Campaign "Hawaii #1", 1 (Box 275)
    - In the Life episode 705: American as Apple Pie 57 minutes, 1998 June-July; 1 (Box 276)
    - Independentlens A Sad Flower in the Sand by Jan Louter (Illinois packaged version) total run time: 56:46, 1 (Box 277)
    - Independentlens Revolucion: Five Visions by Nicole Cattell (Illinois Packaged version) total run time: 56: 46, 1 (Box 278)
    - Indiana presentation "AIDS/Insurance", 1 (Box 279)
    - Inside the Jury Room produced and written by Stephen J. Herzberg, 1 (Box 280)
    - Interview with the Danny Fontana Show, 1 (Box 281)
    - Investigative reports "For Better or Worse: Same Sex Marriages in America" Kurtis Productions, Ltd., 1 (Box 282)
    - J:C:A assignment Backs Against the Wall Gay Rights in the US, 1 (Box 283)
    - Jerusalem is Proud to Present, a film by Nitzan Gilady, 1 (Box 284)
    - Jim in Bold, produced by Equality Forum Glenn Holsten, director Malcom Lazin, executive producer, 1 (Box 285)
    - Jordan Erickson, 1 (Box 286)
    - Judy Nelson: Marriage and the Law Unity, 1994; 1 (Box 287)
    - Justice Talking: Gay Marriage total run time 58:36, 1 (Box 288)
    - Justice Vision, 1 (Box 289)
    - "Karen and Rachel Anne's Wedding", 1995 July 1; 1 (Box 290)
    - Karen Williams comedian, 1 (Box 291)
    - Kismia: samples 817:921:1881, 1 (Box 292)
    - KRON "Gay Marriage" (3 part series), 1995 May 22-24; 1 (Box 293)
    - KRON "Gay Marriage" (3 part series) c. 2, 1995 May 22-24; 1 (Box 294)
    - KRON "Gay Marriage" (3 part series) c. 3, 1995 May 22-24; 1 (Box 295)
    - Lambda "In the Life", 1 (Box 296)
    - Lambda conversation - sorry 1st h2tb only, 1995 June 7; 1 (Box 297)
    - Lambda Legal promotional video running time 4:32, 2008–2009; 1 (Box 298)
    - Lamda Legal Defense and Education Fund, inc. CNN Crossfire, 1 (Box 299)
    - Larry King -> lisp cluster lolk ->2:26, 1 (Box 300)
    - Lavender Law conference, 2004; 1 (Box 301)
    - Lavender Law program materials, 2003; 1 (Box 302)
    - Legal issues "Brooklyn Law School Same-Sex Marriage Forum" 021, 1 (Box 303)
    - Legal Issues "Highlights of 25 Years of Legal Advocacy" 018, 1 (Box 304)
    - LGBTQI CSPAN "State of the Gay Movement" panel 005, 1995 April 20; 1 (Box 305)
    - Like Magic Entertainment INC Kids-TV AIDS *final date: length: 26:32, 1990 May 31; 1 (Box 306)
    - Log Cabin Republicans: Defend the Constitution, 1 (Box 307)
    - Love Knows No Borders Work in Progress Beth Bird, 1 (Box 308)
    - Love Makes a Family: Lesbian and Gay Families in the Religious Society of Friends, 1992; 1 (Box 309)
    - Love Makes a Family: Vermont Civil Union…Is Connecticut next? Wesleyan University, filmed by Chris Sesta, 2001 January 30; 1 (Box 310)
    - Loving Nancy Burski, 1 (Box 311)
    - Magic Box Films: Better Angels, 1 (Box 312)
    - Magic Box Films: Better Angels, 1 (Box 313)
    - Man from Hope, 1 (Box 314)
    - Marc Patlan for Creative, 1 (Box 315)
    - Marc Wolf Another American: Asking and Telling CNN NewsStand report 10 minutes, 1 (Box 316)
    - Marc Wolf NPR: Leonard Lopate 12:07, 2000 January; 1 (Box 317)
    - Marriage debate part I opening, 1 (Box 318)
    - Marriage debate part II debate & closing, 1 (Box 319)
    - Marriage Equality Resource Notebooks National gay and lesbian taskforce, 1 (Box 320)
    - Marriage Equality Resource Notebooks National gay and lesbian taskforce (Box 321)
    - "Marriage Matters" (Davidson, Aronow), 1 (Box 322)
    - MassEquality Education Fund Better Angels, 1 (Box 323)
    - Memorial tribute to Richard Taylor & celebration of our 50 years of love, 1 (Box 324)
    - Miscellaneous - Saints + Sinners 019 (copy 2), 1 (Box 325)
    - MNN TV "Gay USA", 2003 June 26; 1 (Box 326)
    - Mr. And Mrs. Loving (interracial marriage), 1996; 1 (Box 327)
    - MSNBC News Live DVD clip, 2007 February 7; 1 (Box 328)
    - MTV News Now I Do, But I Can't: Gay Marriage in America producer: Ryal Kroft, 2004 March 26; 1 (Box 329)
    - MTV Rock the Vote "Sextoys" "Threat" "Piercings" "Hotdogs" "Donut", 1 (Box 330)
    - My Brother's Keeper TV movie - Tom Bradley, 1995; 1 (Box 331)
    - NABJ: National Association of Black Journalists 30th Anniversary celebration DVD, 1 (Box 332)
    - Naked New York "Marriage/Bob Berkowitz", 2003 April 1; 1 (Box 333)
    - National Engagement Party: program DVD, 1 (Box 334)
    - National Engagement Party: program DVD (Box 335)
    - NBC nightly news "Marriage", 1996 March 25; 1 (Box 336)
    - National Black Lesbian Conference (NBLC) -- Dallas Texas April 7-10 organized by Zuna Institute & Women of Distinction, 2005 April 7-10; 1 (Box 337)
    - National Center for Lesbian Rights (NCLR) discrimination database, 1 (Box 338)
    - New Jersey Tonight #457, 1992 April 28; 1 (Box 339)
    - New York Hotline EP# 101 "John Doe Story", 1 (Box 340)
    - Newstalk - Denise Richardson "Marriage", 1995 June 7; 1 (Box 341)
    - Newstalk - Lisa Maria segment, 1995 September 20; 1 (Box 342)
    - NewsTalk "Civil Rights in Employment", 1995 November 3; 1 (Box 343)
    - NewsTalk "Republican Gay Bashing & Marr.", 1996 February 14; 1 (Box 344)
    - NewsTalk TV "Marriage - Ithaca/Commission", 1995 November 5; 1 (Box 345)
    - Newstalk TV "Same Sex Marriage", 1 (Box 346)
    - Nightline "Marriage" (FRC, Lambda), 1995 September 25; 1 (Box 347)
    - Nightline "Marriage" (FRC, Lambda), 1 (Box 348)
    - No on Knight/No on 22 Complete Campaign Spots & House Party Video, 2 (Box 349–350)
    - NPR - "Gay Marriage", 2003 October 31; 1 (Box 351)
    - New York City Pride day "The Wedding Party Speech" 021, 2001 June 24; 1 (Box 352)
    - One Thousand Plus Frank Feldman, 1 (Box 353)
    - One Wedding and a Revolution directed by Debra Chasnoff women's educational media closed captioned total running time: 19:25, 2004; 1 (Box 354)
    - Oprah, 1 (Box 355)
    - Organizing for initiatives + referenda, 2004 November 11; 1 (Box 356)
    - Out of the Past directed and produced by Jeff Dupre, 1 (Box 357)
    - Pearl Report same-sex marriage featuring Roddy Shaw, Nelson Ng, Rainbow Action, Bishop Joseph Zen and Glen Rhodes United Church (for education purpose only), 2003 September 28; 1 (Box 358)
    - People are Talking Human Rights Campaign, 1989 June 6; 1 (Box 359)
    - Permanent Brasil Atend, 1 (Box 360)
    - Phila Bar podcast, 2008 September 15; 1 (Box 361)
    - Philadelphia NPR "leaders forum" EW, Kate Kendall, Eliz Birch, Becky Mayor, 2003 May 2; 1 (Box 362)
    - Post-it note says No, 1 (Box 363)
    - Post-it says Index - See Luic?, 1 (Box 364)
    - Pride & Progress - Post Hardwick (at 411), 1 (Box 365)
    - Promotional video Gay Cable Network, 1 (Box 366)
    - Publicis MTV "Rock the Vote" 2 spots "piercing" and "threat", 2004 September 17; 1 (Box 367)
    - Publicis Rock the Vote "sex toys" :30 "Threat" :30 "Piercings" :30 "Hotdog" :30 "Donut" :30 "Permission" :60 "Permission" :30, 1 (Box 368)
    - Queer Nation episode 40, 1 (Box 369)
    - Question of Equality #3 Hollow Liberty: A Testing the Limits production, 1 (Box 370)
    - Question of Equality show #101 Outrage '69: A Testing the Limits production, 1995 October 6; 1 (Box 371)
    - Question of Equality show #102 Culture Wars: A Testing the Limits production, 1 (Box 372)
    - Question of Equality show #104 Generation Q: A Testing the Limits production, 1 (Box 373)
    - Question One: a film by Joe Fox and James Nubile preview NTSC DVD region free, 1 (Box 374)
    - Question One: a film by Joe Fox & James Nubile NTSC DVD region free, 1 (Box 375)
    - "Question" "Family" "Al Miyasato" "Jean Aoki" (i30 each) Hawaii, 1998 August; 1 (Box 376)
    - Research material on same-sex marriage compiled by the National LGBTQ Task Force (NGTLF) & The Gill Foundation, 2004 May 10; 1 (Box 377)
    - Richard Taylor & Ray Vahey reception Fair Wisconsin fundraiser remarks & interviews, 1 (Box 378)
    - Right to Marry by Demian Sweet Corn productions, 1 (Box 379)
    - Right to Marry by Demian Sweet Corn productions, 1 (Box 380)
    - Rolonda "Gay Marriage: Should It Be Legal?" Evan Wolfson, Antoinette Pregil, Tammy Rodrigues Show #RL4120, 1997 February 11-1997 February 27; 1 (Box 381)
    - Rush to the Civil Altar documentary feature "Work In Progress", 1 (Box 382)
    - Saints & Sinners screener total run time 71:00, 1 (Box 383)
    - "Same Sex Marriage" Henrique Faria, 1 (Box 384)
    - Same-sex double wedding, 1 (Box 385)
    - Same-Sex Marriage: A Civil Debate "The Opposition" The Gill Foundation and Focus on the Family, 1 (Box 386)
    - Same-sex marriage A Civil Debate, February 24 2004; 10 (Box 387–396)
      - Same-Sex marriage: a civil debate, 2016-M-0049-0139; 1 (Box 387)
      - Same-Sex marriage: a civil debate, 2016-M-0049-0140; 1 (Box 388)
      - Same-Sex marriage: a civil debate, 2016-M-0049-0141; 1 (Box 389)
      - Same-Sex marriage: a civil debate, 2016-M-0049-0142; 1 (Box 390)
      - Same-Sex marriage: a civil debate, 2016-M-0049-0143; 1 (Box 391)
      - Same-Sex marriage: a civil debate, 2016-M-0049-0144; 1 (Box 392)
      - Same-Sex marriage: a civil debate, 2016-M-0049-0145; 1 (Box 393)
      - Same-Sex marriage: a civil debate, 2016-M-0049-0146; 1 (Box 394)
      - Same-Sex marriage: a civil debate, 2016-M-0049-0147; 1 (Box 395)
      - Same-Sex marriage: a civil debate, 2016-M-0049-0148; 1 (Box 396)
    - Same-sex marriage feature and cityscape, February 24 2004; 1 (Box 397)
    - Same-Sex Marriage: A Civil Debate opposition sponsored by The Gill Foundation & Focus on the Family, February 24 2004; 1 (Box 398)
    - Saving Marriage 2.26.08 screener 90 min Documix Films LLC Contact: Mike Roth, 2007; 1 (Box 399)
    - Saving Marriage Get Ready, 1 (Box 400)
    - Savoy King: Chick Webb and the Music that Changed America, 1 (Box 401)
    - Seamans Company Human Rights Campaign Marriage 101 :30 Spin 104 :30, 1996 July 30; 1 (Box 402)
    - Senate floor session total running time: 01:30:00 Disc 1 of 1, 2005 September 1; 1 (Box 403)
    - Show no. 101, ch. 1/2 - program line cut, 1 (Box 404)
    - Showtime "Marriage", 1999 June 14; 1 (Box 405)
    - Speech at William & Mary "Marriage Discrimination", 1999 March 22; 1 (Box 406)
    - Speech: Grand Rapids, Michigan, 1 (Box 407)
    - Stein Scholars roundtable, FLS Evan Wolfson, Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1999 November 17; 1 (Box 408)
    - Stephanie Smith Demo, 1 (Box 409)
    - Sunday programme Hawaii package, 1998 June 14; 1 (Box 410)
    - Talk of the Nation: hour 1 same sex marriages, 1996 April 11; 1 (Box 411)
    - Tape #4 "Civil debate" final wedding day speech, 2001 June 24; 1 (Box 412)
    - This Way Out, 1998 November 3; 1 (Box 413)
    - This Way Out dolby B, 2000 January 31; 1 (Box 414)
    - This Way Out dolby B, 2003 June 16; 1 (Box 415)
    - This Way Out dolby B, 2004 August 16; 1 (Box 416)
    - TLJR live town hall meeting "Same Sex Marriage" show #051304, 2004 May 13; 1 (Box 417)
    - Total Living Network town hall meeting same-sex marriage - 051304, 1 (Box 418)
    - Talk of the Nation (TOTN) same-sex marriage KCUR-FM :50min, 1996 April 8; 1 (Box 419)
    - Trials of Jimmy Creech: One man's courageous stand for God's lesbian & gay children a pre-trial interview by Dr. Mel White, 1 (Box 420)
    - Tying the Knot (documentary trailer), 1 (Box 421)
    - Tying the Knot 4 minute preview DVD www.1049films.com, 1 (Box 422)
      - Tying the Knot 4 min. trailer, 2016-M-0049-0156; 1 (Box 422)
    - Tying the Knot 4 minute preview DVD www.1049films.com, 1 (Box 423)
    - Tying the Knot 4 minute trailer, 1 (Box 424)
    - Tying the Knot 4 minute trailer, 1 (Box 425)
    - Tying the Knot 4 minute trailer, 1 (Box 426)
    - Tying the Knot 4 minute trailer, 1 (Box 427)
    - Tying the Knot fundraising showreel running time: 13 minutes, 1 (Box 428)
    - Ultimate Target of the Gay Agenda: Same Sex marriages the report, 1996; 1 (Box 429)
    - University sen. plenary, 1999 October 20; 1 (Box 430)
    - University sen. plenary tape 2, 1999 October 20; 1 (Box 431)
    - USA Today Live gay marriage, 1 (Box 432)
    - Vickie Shaw comedian, 1 (Box 433)
    - Voice of America legal window Chinese Branch voice of Washington DC in Chinese 1. Gay/Lesbian laws: same-sex marriage, 2004; 1 (Box 434)
    - Wedrock Los Angeles photos, 1 (Box 436)
    - Wed-rock recorded live in New York City, 2006; 1 (Box 437)
    - Weekend Edition Sunday Bishop's letter marriage MK NPR, 1 (Box 438)
    - WFAA-TV 8 same sex marriage, 1 (Box 439)
    - WI Pullu rodeo Canada, 2003 June; 1 (Box 440)
    - Winnipeg CBA Canadian legal conference and expo 2004, 1 (Box 441)
    - Zimmerman & Markman moveon.org, 1 (Box 442)
  - Evan Wolfson material, 1986-2013
    - Boy Scouts Jeff Simmons, 1 (Box 443)
    - Boy Scouts of America and Monmouth council, et al vs. James Dale, 2000 April 26; 1 (Box 444)
    - Boy Scouts of America and Monmouth council, et al. vs. James Dale, 2000 April 26; 1 (Box 445)
    - Boy Scouts of America and Monmouth council, et al. vs. James Dale, 2000 April 26; 1 (Box 446)
    - Boy Scouts of America and Monmouth council, et al. vs. James Dale, 2000 April 26 (Box 447)
    - City Club of Cleveland Friday forum series Evan Wolfson, executive director, Freedom to Marry, 2004 June 11; 1 (Box 448)
    - City Club of Cleveland: Evan Wolfson - Freedom to Marry, 2004 June 11; 1 (Box 449)
    - CNN's situation room Evan Wolfson, 2007 June 26; 1 (Box 450)
    - CourtTV Evan Wolfson Florida, 1 (Box 451)
    - CourtTV Evan's Hawaii case, 1996 September 30; 1 (Box 452)
    - Dale v. Boy Scouts hearing Supreme Court of New Jersey, 1999 January 5; 2 (Box 453–454)
    - Dale v. Boy Scouts of America oral argument New Jersey appellate court, 1997 December 8; 1 (Box 455)
    - Dale vs. Boy Scouts hearing, 1999 January 8; 1 (Box 456)
    - Danny Fontana Show DF-6211 gay marriage guest: Wolfson media comm, 2006 December 6; 1 (Box 457)
    - Dateline "Scout's Honor", 1999 August 24; 1 (Box 458)
    - "Dialogue 101" 5:00am Evan Wolfson-Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund, inc., 1991 June 9; 1 (Box 459)
    - DI Franken Show 6/23 Evan Wolfson, 1 (Box 460)
    - Evan + Matthew Shepherd hearing, 1 (Box 461)
    - Evan court 3:45; day at whahm 4:45, 1 (Box 462)
    - Evan Larry King, 1 (Box 463)
    - Evan Wolfson "Are gay rights special rights?" Princeton University, May 5 1994; 1 (Box 464)
    - Evan Wolfson "Crossfire" tape 2, 1 (Box 465)
    - Evan Wolfson "The O'Reilly Factor" "Fox & Friends", 1 (Box 466)
    - Evan Wolfson "Evan Wolfson v. John Street" debate 020, 1999 May 21; 1 (Box 467)
    - Evan Wolfson Court TV, 1996 December 3; 1 (Box 468)
    - Evan Wolfson Court TV: Hawaii, Deus and FFC, 1996 December 4; 1 (Box 469)
    - Evan Wolfson court to Florida, 1 (Box 470)
    - Evan Wolfson hi-res shot (use Evan-2) 2 backups in folder, 1 (Box 471)
    - Evan Wolfson on Situation Room (full and web quality copy), 1 (Box 472)
    - Evan Wolfson Regional News Network 7:00pm, 2004 July 13; 1 (Box 473)
    - Evan Wolfson tape #1: "Why Marriage Matters", 1 (Box 474)
    - Evan Wolfson tape #3 "Civil Debate: Same-Sex Marriage", 1 (Box 475)
    - Evan Wolfson tape #5: "Face of the Nation, CNN", 2003 June 19; 1 (Box 476)
    - Evan Wolfson tape #6 "PBA Forum on Same Sex", 1997 May 21; 1 (Box 477)
    - Evan Wolfson WPR, 2007 April 11; 1 (Box 478)
    - Evan Wolfson WUSA 9News at 9am, 2004 July 22; 1 (Box 479)
    - Evan Wolfson: "O'Reilly Factor" & "Fox and Friends", 2004 June 13-14; 1 (Box 480)
    - Evan Wolfson: Evan, 1 (Box 481)
    - Evan Wolfson: late 1986, circa 1986; 1 (Box 482)
    - Evan Wolfson: Lavender Law, 2004; 1 (Box 483)
    - Evan Wolfson: Speech at UHI "Same sex marriage", 1 (Box 484)
    - Gay pride speaker-Dickstein Shapiro LLP, 2008 June 24; 1 (Box 485)
    - KKIQ "In Focus", guest Evan Wolfson, topic marriage equality, 2005 July 17; 1 (Box 486)
    - L.20 8/5 Evan Wolfson of Rebecca Corrol KCBS, 1 (Box 487)
    - Lange Money Hour: Where smart money talks Evan Wolfson, 2013 December 4; 1 (Box 488)
    - Larry King Evan, 1 (Box 489)
    - LMA: Evan Wolfson, 1 (Box 490)
    - Nightline Marriage Evan Wolfson Lambda Legal Defense, 1995 August 25; 1 (Box 491)
    - P.I. 89-169 Evan Wolfson focus groups defense/judge prosecution, 1989 January 30; 1 (Box 492)
    - RNN Richard French Live Evan Wolfson interview, 1 (Box 493)
    - Same-sex marriage debate Georgia Law Evan Wolfson & Lynn Wardle, 2004 February 17; 1 (Box 494)
    - "Scouts' Honor" and "South Park (gay scout)", 2001; 1 (Box 495)
    - Too Jewish with Rabbi Sam Cohon and Friends guest: Evan Wolfson director of Freedom to Marry, 1 (Box 496)
    - UCC General Synod Evan Wolfson?, 2005; 1 (Box 497)
    - Update: The Marriage Project Evan Wolfson - Little America Hotel, Family Fellowship and Parents, Families, and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (PFLAG) continued, 1999 June 12; 1 (Box 498)
  - Freedom to Marry press clips, 1996-2001
    - Freedom to Marry and the defense of marriage, 2003; 1 (Box 499)
    - Freedom to Marry town hall meeting, 1996 January 23; 1 (Box 500)
    - Freedom to Marry Weston Crown Kansas City, Missouri tape 1, 1 (Box 501)
    - Freedom to Marry Weston Crown Kansas City, Missouri tape 2, 1 (Box 502)
    - Freedom to Marry: A Green Mountain view, 1 (Box 503)
    - FTM Freedom to Marry #4B "Life after ballot initiatives", 1 (Box 504)
    - FTM Freedom to Marry Week PFLAG, 2009; 1 (Box 505)
    - Gay Talk Radio on Air America, 2006 February 12; 1 (Box 506)
    - Gay Talk Radio On Air America (Box 507)
    - RSVP productions Freedom to Marry Weston Crown Center Kansas City, Missouri, tape 1, 2006 November 9; 1 (Box 508)
    - RSVP productions Freedom to Marry Weston Crown Center Kansas City, Missouri, tape 1, 2006 November 9; 1 (Box 509)
    - RSVP productions Freedom to Marry Weston Crown Center Kansas City, Missouri, Tape 2, 2006 November 9; 1 (Box 510)
    - RSVP productions Freedom to Marry Weston Crown Center Kansas City, Missouri, Tape 2, 2006 November 9; 1 (Box 511)
    - Unitarian Universalist Church of Berkeley Freedom to Marry, 1 (Box 512)
  - Freedom to Marry-produced material, 2004-2011
    - Dearly Beloved California Freedom to Marry Coalition produced by Sylvia Rhue, 1 (Box 513)
    - F2M images, 2007 December; 1 (Box 514)
    - Freedom to Marry banners "Wall Posters", 1 (Box 515)
    - Freedom to Marry - single logos stylesheet for loop usage, 1 (Box 516)
    - Freedom to Marry collateral photos For Richer, For Poorer - non gay allies - annual report, 2006–2007; 1 (Box 517)
    - Freedom to Marry copy Fisher Family Hall JCCSF, 2007 June 19; 1 (Box 518)
    - Freedom to Marry panel discussion National Black Justice Coalition, 1 (Box 519)
    - Freedom to Marry Red Tettemer, 1 (Box 520)
    - Freedom to Marry Red Tettemer, 1 (Box 521)
    - Freedom to Marry: Voices of Vermonters, 1 (Box 522)
    - FTM RF Images, 1 (Box 523)
    - In the Life Media Freedom to Marry PSA including: 1-Cristina and Monica 2-George and Farid 3-Tobi and Janee, 2011 April; 1 (Box 524)
    - Movement for Marriage equality in the United States: a timeline by Ken Molsberry for review by Freedom to Marry only (do not distribute), 2005; 1 (Box 525)
    - Winning the Freedom to Marry 1, 2004 November 11; 1 (Box 526)
    - Winning the Freedom to Marry 2, 2004 November 11; 1 (Box 527)
    - Winning the Freedom to Marry 3, 2004 November 11; 1 (Box 528)
    - Winning the Freedom to Marry 4, 2004 November 11; 1 (Box 529)
    - Winning the Freedom to Marry 5, 2004 November 11; 1 (Box 530)
    - Winning the Freedom to Marry 6, 2004 November 11; 1 (Box 531)
    - Winning the Freedom to Marry 7, 2004 November 11; 1 (Box 532)
    - Winning the Freedom to Marry This Decade, 1 (Box 533)
- Additional material, Accession 2018-M-0045
  - Computer files, Circa 2000-2015; 2018-m-0045-0001; 1 (Box 1)
    The computer files are unprocessed and may contain sensitive information or be in a physical state that would prohibit use. Researchers wishing to request access should email mssa.assist@yale.edu. The request should outline the scope and purpose of the research project, why the researcher believes the material is relevant to their project, and contact information. If possible the request should also include a list of specific material of interest including collection, box, and folder numbers (or folder descriptions if folders are not numbered). The review may take several weeks.